{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\chapter9.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "E' l'una di notte.",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1459791756.7708874,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"It's 1:00 am\"?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lei fa il medico.",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1459791680.2126455,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She is a medical doctor.\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sono le undici e un quarto di mattina.",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1459791824.4299617,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"It's 11:15am\"?",
            "tried": 16
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'imprenditrice",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1459791711.3795526,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the businesswoman\"?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "answer": "the clerk (male)",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1459791762.6712613,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'impiegato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "answer": "Fai l'ingegnere.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1459791809.8622317,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You are an engineer.\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'operaia",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1459791634.0005977,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the worker (female)\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'imprenditore",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1459791788.5309546,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the businessman\"?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'insegnante",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1459791996.7037437,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the teacher\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "answer": "Faccio l'avvocato",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1459791926.388595,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am a lawyer.\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'artista",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1459791885.8339496,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the artist\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lei fa l'architetto.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1459791944.3365564,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She is an architect.\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "answer": "E' mezzogiorno.",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1459792014.0480065,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"It's noon.\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "answer": "I work on Mondays and Thursdays.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459791895.033268,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io lavoro il lundedi e il giovedi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "Ci vediamo alle sette e mezzo.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1459792008.5996242,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Let's meet at 7:30\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "answer": "il commerciante",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1459791977.8677938,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the vendor (male)\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sei un dottore.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1459792232.3213902,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You are a doctor. (male)\"?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lovorare dal lunedi al venerdi.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1459792224.0648928,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to work from Monday to Friday\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "answer": "Che ora e'? Che ore sono?",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1459792157.1785488,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"What's the time?\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'impiegata",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1459792104.3264365,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the clerk (female)\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "giovedi",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459792139.8064418,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Thursday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lui/Lei non lavora il sabato e la domenica.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1459792189.3300855,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She doesn't work on Saturdays and Sundays.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "di pomeriggio",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459792211.6534936,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in the afternoon (from 1 to 5pm)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sono le due.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792175.0219066,
            "question": "Given the definition \"It's two o'clock.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "the worker (female)",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792265.5487537,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'operaia\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sono una professoressa.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1459792413.94686,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am a professor (female).\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'impiegato",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1459792373.7152405,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the clerk (male)\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "answer": "martedi",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459792381.1592374,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tuesday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sei una dottoressa.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792367.2899182,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You are a doctor. (female)\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Il viaggio e' durato due ore e mezza.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1459792399.326372,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The trip lasted two and a half hours.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "Wednesday",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1459792404.886926,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"mercoledi\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "l'operaio",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459792377.68339,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the worker (male)\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "the teacher",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459792434.8271472,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'insegnante\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "answer": "il lunedi",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459792536.929113,
            "question": "Given the definition \"on Mondays\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "the businesswoman",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792503.1975374,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'imprenditrice\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "E' mezzanotte.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792511.2934911,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"It's midnight.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "Tu lavori il martedi, il mercoledi e il venerdi.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459792556.2441843,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You work on Tuesdays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "You work on Tuesdays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792497.4856358,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu lavori il martedi, il mercoledi e il venerdi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "in the night (from midnight to 3am)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792533.4414513,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di notte\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "to work from Monday to Friday",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792431.5539937,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lovorare dal lunedi al venerdi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "mercoledi",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792635.8712528,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Wednesday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's 1:00 am",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792632.519041,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E' l'una di notte.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "the vendor (male)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792599.9164555,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il commerciante\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "in the evening (from 6 to 11pm)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792625.5756955,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di sera\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lui fa l'architetto.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1459792652.3633547,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He is an architect.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "di sera",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792612.53899,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in the evening (from 6 to 11pm)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's noon.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792594.8843777,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E' mezzogiorno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "the clerk (female)",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792607.2683005,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'impiegata\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "You are a doctor. (male)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792659.915177,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sei un dottore.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "in the afternoon (from 1 to 5pm)",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1459792739.4306178,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di pomeriggio\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "She is an architect.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792717.5867167,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei fa l'architetto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "The trip lasted two and a half hours.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792677.5419328,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Il viaggio e' durato due ore e mezza.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "You are an engineer.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792683.7353253,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Fai l'ingegnere.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "on Mondays",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792690.8707266,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il lunedi\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sono un professore.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792730.6386063,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am a professor (male).\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "She is a medical doctor.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792665.966883,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei fa il medico.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "the vender (female)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792757.8505628,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la commerciante\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "the businessman",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1459792751.290395,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'imprenditore\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Tuesday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792761.1140296,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"martedi\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's two o'clock.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792782.8457124,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Sono le due.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sunday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792746.5343,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"domenica\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "lunedi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792743.4778504,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Monday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "He/She doesn't work on Saturdays and Sundays.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792776.870268,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui/Lei non lavora il sabato e la domenica.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "in the morning (from 4 to 11am)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792801.241872,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di mattina\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "domenica",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792835.7728462,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sunday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "He is an architect.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792816.2494462,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui fa l'architetto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "la commerciante",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792832.237361,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the vender (female)\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "You are a doctor. (female)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792843.5012095,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sei una dottoressa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Friday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792805.6405072,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"venerdi\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Saturday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792810.8576171,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sabato\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "venerdi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792808.416984,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Friday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "What's the time?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792822.7128077,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Che ora e'? Che ore sono?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "di mattina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792863.3767097,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in the morning (from 4 to 11am)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "I am a lawyer.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792859.384789,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Faccio l'avvocato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lui fa il medico.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792854.4970567,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He is a medical doctor.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "the artist",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792867.9760337,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'artista\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "di notte",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792886.5244641,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in the night (from midnight to 3am)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's midnight.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792880.9766676,
            "question": "Given the definition \"E' mezzanotte.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Thursday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792893.652214,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"giovedi\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's 11:15am",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792876.016063,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sono le undici e un quarto di mattina.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "the worker (male)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792920.3919563,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'operaio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Let's meet at 7:30",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792956.7356813,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Ci vediamo alle sette e mezzo.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "sabato",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792906.2922366,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Saturday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "I am a professor (female).",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792947.6951563,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sono una professoressa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "I am a professor (male).",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792903.5484066,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Sono un professore.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "He is a medical doctor.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792912.359336,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui fa il medico.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Io lavoro il lundedi e il giovedi.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792936.042425,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I work on Mondays and Thursdays.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Monday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1459792915.6402686,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lunedi\"?",
            "tried": 3
        }
    ]
}